

Full Stack Web Developer

jaydenj772@gmail.com 0782386120

Cape Town, South Africa

Blessing Jackson

Profile

I am a Full stack web developer with 1 year of experience in web development. I am working with different technologies including React, Node.js, ruby, ruby on rails, express Js, MongoDB, NoSQL, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript and popular frameworks such as bootstrap, tailwind CSS, material design.

Employment History

Full Stack Developer at Shufti, Cape Town

03/2023-Present

- Perfoming coding, debugging, and unit testing tasks in support of projects.
- Providing ongoing maintenance for assigned applications and systems.
- Appliying current programming standards and methodologies to all relevant projects and activities.
- Upgrading and maintaining both the back-end and front-end systems.
- Working alongside web developers, marketing teams, and engineers to ensure the right look and vital features are being achieved.
- Remaining adaptable and committed to stay on top of growing technologies and engineering trends.
- Developing scalable web-based user interfaces and components using Node.js, React.js

Full Stack Developer at Upwork.com, Upwork.com

08/2021—Present

- Collaborating with a team of engineers and developers.
- Developing and designing front end web architecture with high responsiveness of applications,
- Working with other departments to address improvements, internal tools, and implementation issues.
- Consistently appliying best practices for writing clean, secure, readable, and scalable code.
- Participating in meaningful and thorough code reviews.

Links

Portfolio LinkedIn Github repositories

Skills

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Express.js	4/5
SQL, React.js, Node.js, Next.js	3/5
Craft cms	3/5
Python	2/5
Teamwork	4/5
Time Management	3/5
Ability to Multitask, Adaptability	3/5
Fast Learner	4/5
Leadership Skills	5/5
Complex Problem Solving	3/5
Design and Development of APIs	3/5

Languages

English	Highly proficient
Shona	Native speaker
Afrikaans	Good working knowledge

Hobbies

Soccer.

Education

DIPLOMA IN FRESH EXPRESSIONS, Hugenote College SA, Cape Town

01/2018-12/2019

Graduated with higher score

Higher certification in IT Technician , Young Africa Skills College , Harare

01/2012-12/2012